[{"answer": "Yeah, well a couple of things have changed.  It ain't gonna be the my friend story no more. Goddamn", "docId": "Ed-Wood.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "No, of COURSE I'm gonna make the movie!  I've already presold that place and that place.  Those repressed Okies really go for that twisted pervert stuff.  So we'll just make it without that sh", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Nah, I'm all man.  I even fought in WW2.  'Course, I  wearing ladies' undergarments under my uniform", "docId": "Ed-Wood.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Confidentially, I even paratrooped wearing a brassiere and panties. I'll tell ya, I wasn't scared of being killed, but I was  of getting wounded, and having the medics discover my secret", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Sweetie, you won't believe it!  I've got the most incredible news", "docId": "Ed-Wood.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Huh?!  Oh, uh, no, I didn't get the job. But something  happened", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " You got the job?!", "docId": "Ed-Wood.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Better than not getting a job", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "one", "docId": "Ed-Wood.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Oh, the hell with you.  I met my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "!\", \"dependency_gramma", "docId": "Ed-Wood.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " No, he's not dead!  He lives in that place.  I met him recently, and he wants to be in our picture", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " No, he's not dead!  He lives in that place.  I met him recently, and he wants to be in our picture", "docId": "Ed-Wood.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " Uh, yeah.  Our picture", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Well... you control everyone's fate. You're like the puppetmaster", "docId": "Ed-Wood.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Yeah.  You pull the strings", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Eh, forget it.  What else is big?  Teenagers!  Jailbait pics!  Yeah... You got the juvenile delinquent, his girlfriend from the wrong side of the tracks", "docId": "Ed-Wood.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Uh, a cop.  NO!  You play the father. He's !  He doesn't like seeing his son", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " That's good.  I could use the money", "docId": "Ed-Wood.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " Hmm... my biggest hit?  That would probably be", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "What the hell is this?", "docId": "Ed-Wood.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "It can't be", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I didn't feel well..", "docId": "Ed-Wood.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "No hospital.  Just take me to the couch..", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "And who may you be", "docId": "Ed-Wood.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Ah.  The director of", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Ah.  The director of", "docId": "Ed-Wood.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I'm my friend.  I know all", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Tell him", "docId": "Ed-Wood.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "cares about my movie!  I'm tryin' so hard, I don't know what else to do", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "cares about my movie!  I'm tryin' so hard, I don't know what else to do", "docId": "Ed-Wood.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": " my friend, don't you understand?  I'm a director now!  I made", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "What other sixt", "docId": "Ed-Wood.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "You misunderstood.  I gave you everything I have in the worl", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "\"Our government wants you to return... to continue your experiments there.  Where you can have everything at your disposal", "docId": "Ed-Wood.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "\"Yes, the authorities have learned how correct your findings were.  So I am here", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Booties for my father.  He gets cold in this hospital", "docId": "Ed-Wood.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "This is my thirteenth pair", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "No! I love sex with girls", "docId": "Ed-Wood.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": " Okay", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "That cardboard headstone tipped over. This graveyard is obviously phony", "docId": "Ed-Wood.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Oh, you wanna talk about the", "qsentId": 42}]